gliq.com 2016-06-13

# Global IntelliSystems: Privacy Statement

Main Offices  
1153 Bergen Parkway, #455  
Evergreen, CO 80439  
Main Office Direct: (970) 315-3637  
Palo Alto Office: (650) 433-6079 

To assist in the ease-of-reading we have summarized our privacy statement into separate easy to understand sections. If you have any questions please contact us using the information provided above.

CONSUMER PRIVACY NOTICE

To comply with various Federal and/or State regulations, we are advising you of the action taken with personally identifiable information (PII) that takes place between you and our service, including our website.

PII COLLECTION: NO Visiting our website will remain private between you and us. None of your PII is collected, saved, stored, sold or bartered based on your visit to our website.

EMAIL PRIVACY: YES Email communications from you are not used for any marketing purposes. We will not add your email address to a list unless you specifically request us to take that action. Any email from you to any of our employees is treated as company private information and never resold or given to anyone.

REVERSE PII: NO. We do not work with any direct or third party vendors to obtain any PII about you based on your IP address, browser session data, or any other method of obtaining PII. Your visit to our website will not be shared with anyone outside our firm, and it will never be used for any marketing purpose.

PII FOR PAYMENT: YES. The only information we share with a third party, and the ONLY third party, is our credit card processing service. Your PII is limited to Name, Address, City, State, Zip Code, Telephone Number, Credit Card Number, and amount of charge. This limited credit card PII is kept in a physical safe and is not stored online.

REGISTRATION

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and/or create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give us contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. Upon registration, you will receive our monthly "Tech Titan" newsletter which describes the state of the industry, future projections, and email marketing trends. Global IntelliSystems is the sole owner of the information collected on the www.GlobalintelliSystems.com website. Global IntelliSystems collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. You will receive an email from us upon your purchase describing the product(s) purchased, estimated installation date, and a confirmation of the purchase itself.

FOR RECIPIENTS — HOW YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS IS LOCATED

Our customers maintain strict opt-in and confirmed-opt-in policies on their own websites. You only receive mail from our clients if you subscribe to their lists. You will receive a confirmation email within minutes of subscribing and most of the time you will be required to click on a link inside that confirmation to verify you want to subscribe. This is known as "double opt-in" or "verified opt-in" and we encourage ALL of our clients to use this form of opt-in.

We do not, ever, allow customers to harvest, collect, purchase, rent, or acquire email address lists, period. We maintain one of the strictest no-spam policies on the Internet. Customers are trained, often by us, on the proper methods to use when setting up their mailing list. Often when you subscribe to a client list you will receive mailings from that client the same day and sometimes a few times per week. This is standard practice for many clients but you have total control over what you receive, when, and how much you receive. Our clients will always give you the option to adjust the frequency of mailing.

When you unsubscribe from the client list your address is IMMEDIATELY removed and stored in a "suppression list" which is a method used by most professional mailers to ensure you never receive mail from the client again.

If you ever have difficulties with one of our clients, we ask that you send us a copy of the content you received and we will perform an audit of your email address on their list to verify, for you, that your address was obtained only by your subscribing to the list. You will be removed from the list instantly, by us, if we are asked to do so.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [support@gliq.com](mailto:support@gliq.com)

USE OF YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS

We do not collect or store your email address from your visit to our website. You are not required to give us your email address when you contact us and if you contact us by email, you may ask for us to destroy your email message after we read it. Your email address may be on a list owned by one of our clients but that client, and only that client, has your address. We do not share databases between clients so if you are on a mailing list, it is not our list, it is sole and exclusive property of our client. Any time you give us an email address for problem resolution it is used in that regard only and is destroyed after the problem has been resolved. We will, however, keep your email address on file if you request us to do so for future contact.

THIRD PARTY DISCLOSURE OF LIMITED PII

We use other third parties to provide credit card processing on our site. When you sign up for our e-mail marketing services, consultant services, or delivery assurance services, we will share only the invoice number and/or your telephone number with the credit card processor at the time of purchase. Your credit card information is never kept on file at Global IntelliSystems and these third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.  
Any information provided while placing an order is collected by our third party service provider. That information is shared with Global Intellisystems. This information includes ordering information such as shipping and billing names and addresses, phone numbers, email addresses. Your credit card information is not shared with us. We use this information primarily to fulfill customers orders and requests.

LAW ENFORCEMENT/LEGAL DISCLOSURE OF PII

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION IN OUR SYSTEM

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making changes directly on our member information page or by requesting a copy of the information by emailing support@gliq.com. You may submit the updates, deletions, or deactivation request back to the same email address or by contacting us by telephone, postal mail, or fax.

SECURITY PRACTICES AND STANDARDS

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [support@gliq.com](mailto:support@gliq.com).

The security of your personal information is important to us. We contract with third parties who use secure socket layer technology (SSL) encryption when you pay your invoice including submitting your credit card number to them to remit payment. No sensitive information is collected on our website.

USE OF TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer, generally in the browser folder, for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site only in the member area once you are logged-into your account. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use session ID cookies only. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie, which we do NOT use, remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. To understand more about cookies please visit this site.

We set a session ID cookie to store your login information so you do not need to re-log-in every time you navagate our site. The cookies are lost the moment you close your browser. In addition, the session ID cookie is triple encrypted using Blowfish, DES, and AES encryption (one layer on top of another) to provide the ultimate layer of security. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as managing your mailings, viewing reports, etc. will be limited.

USE OF YOR NAME

We do not require you give us your name when contacting us nor do we harvest your name or obtain your name by any reverse-IP-matching services on the Internet. We also do not give your name to anyone other than our support department for problem resolution, should you give us your name. Should one of our clients have your name in their database, that database is solely owned by our client and we do not share, sell, rent, or distribute any data from that database, ever.

USE OF YOUR MAILING ADDRESS

We do not require you to give us your address when contacting us nor do we obtain your address by use of a reverse append email-to-street service. Should you give us your mailing address it will be used only in the context that you request it be used. We will not give your mailing address out to anyone, ever, for any reason (other than law enforcement purposes, should it be requested.) Our client may have your mailing address in their database but that database is the sole and exclusive property of our client and we do not share, sell, rent, transfer, or otherwise distribute your mailing address from that database or any database belonging to any client.

USE OF YOUR TELEPHONE NUMBER

We do not require you give us your telephone number when contacting us.

QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS?

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our policy support department at [support@gliq.com](mailto:support@gliq.com) or at 970-315-3637. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

Last Updated on: 08/27/2014
